Finding Aid for Vice President for Government Relations (University of Michigan) records, 1960-1999
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Washington Office Files, 1984-1999
  - 1984-1999
    - Graduate Student Assistant Withholding, 1987-1988 (Box 30)
    - H.A.C.E. (Higher and Adult Continuing Education) Class, 1991-1996 (Box 30)
    - Harris Fellowships, 1989 (Box 30)
    - Henry Facilities Amendment, 1992 (Box 30)
    - House Subcommittee on Post-Secondary Education, 1985 (Box 30)
    - HUD (Housing and Urban Development)-Independent Agencies Coalition, 1989 (Box 30)
    - Illinois, University of, Office of Educational Research and Improvement Application, 1990 (Box 30)
    - Income Contingent Repayment, 1997 (Box 30)
    - Indirect Cost (Research Grant Overhead Charges, includes U of M Audit), 1988-1993; 16 folders (Box 31)
    - Interest Deductions, 1991 (Box 31)
    - International Activities Consortium (MUCIA), 1989 (Box 31)
    - International Issues, 1988-1989 (Box 31)
    - Jacks, Kay (Direct lending), 1994-1995 (Box 32)
    - Jeffords Hearing (Direct Loans), 1995 (Box 32)
    - Joint University Reception (Spontaneous Cooperation Among Michigan Universities), 1990 (Box 32)
    - Kauffman, Bill
      - Agriculture, Space, Po, 1989 (Box 32)
      - National Transportation and Safety Board, 1989-1990 (Box 32)
    - Labor, House Appropriations Committee, 1990 (Box 32)
    - Law School Accreditation, 1990 (Box 32)
    - Legislative Memoranda (University of Michigan), 1987 (Box 32)
    - Loan Flexibility, 1997-1998 (Box 32)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, 1992 (Box 32)
    - Mandatory Retirement, 1988 (Box 32)
    - Mansfield Center Bill, 1989 (Box 32)
    - Michigan Congressional Delegation, 1990-1993 (Box 32)
    - Michigan Student Aid Bills, 1985 (Box 32)
    - Michigan Student Financial Aid Association (MSFAA), 1991 (Box 32)
    - NASA, Mission to Planet Earth, 1989 (Box 32)
    - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges (NASULGC)
      - Duderstadt Federal Legislation Committee, 1990 (Box 32)
      - Student Aid and Legislative Committees, 1987 (Box 32)
    - National Commission on Responsibilities for Financing Postsecondary Education (NCRFPSE), 1991-1993; 3 folders (Box 32)
    - National Education Association (NEA)/ National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH) Reauthorization, 1990 (Box 32)
    - NEA-Sewell Grant, 1989 (Box 32)
    - National Grand Fellows Board, 1987-1988 (Box 32)
    - National Issues Class, 1987-1990 (Box 32)
    - National Science Foundation, 1989-1990 (Box 32)
    - National Service, 1989-1990 (Box 32)
    - Native Americans (Mainly re; Artifact Repatriation), 1989-1992 (Box 32)
    - Network Ad Hoc Tax Group, 1987-1989; 2 folders (Box 32)
    - Non-Profit Organizations, 1993 (Box 32)
    - OMB Accounting Rules, 1993 (Box 32)
    - Origination Fee (Harkin Amendment), 1998 (Box 33)
    - Peace Institute Reauthorization, 1988 (Box 33)
    - Pell Processing, 1989 (Box 33)
    - Public Service Intern Program, 1989 (Box 33)
    - Research Libraries-Title II, 1985-1989 (Box 33)
    - Research Roundtable, University/ Industry, 1990 (Box 33)
    - Schembechler, Bo, visit with President Bush, 1990 (Box 33)
    - Secretaries of Education (Former), 1995 (Box 33)
    - Section 89 Tax Legislation, 1988-1989 (Box 33)
    - Senate Committee on Governmental Affairs (Indirect Cost), 1991-1992 (Box 33)
    - Small Business Hearing (Doug Van Houweling Testimony), 1985 (Box 33)
    - Small Business Hearing (Doug Van Houweling Testimony), 1988 (Box 33)
    - SPREs (State Postsecondary Review Entities) and Accreditation, 1994 (Box 33)
    - Student Lending Update, 1996-1997 (Box 33)
    - Sunrayce (University of Michigan Solar Car), 1990 (Box 33)
    - Superconducting Super Collider, 1990 (Box 33)
    - Tax Organization, 1984 (Box 33)
    - Tax Proposals, 1991 (Box 33)
    - Tax Section 457, 1987 (Box 33)
    - TIAA-CREF, 1997 (Box 33)
    - Treasury Report (Financial Viability of the Government-Guaranteed Student Loan Program), 1998 (Box 33)
    - Tuition Collusion-Justice Department, 1989 (Box 33)
    - Tuition Prepayment Plans, 1987 (Box 33)
    - Tuition Reimbursement, 1995 (Box 33)
    - UBIT (Unrelated Business Income Tax)
      - 1986-1989, 4 folders (Box 33)
      - Alumni Travel, 1988 (Box 33)
      - Research, 1988-1989 (Box 33)
      - University of Michigan Position, 1988-1989 (Box 33)
    - University of Michigan
      - Alumni Club of DC, 1984-1991 (Box 33)
      - DC Office (undated) (Box 33)
      - Student Conduct, 1989 (Box 33)
    - University Small Business Research Technology Consortium, 1987 (Box 33)
    - URI, 1987 (Box 33)
    - Volunteer Early Retirement Incentive Plans (VERIP), 1997-1998 (Box 33)
    - Washington Group, 1989 (Box 33)
    - Willow Run, 1990 (Box 33)
    - Zajonc, Robert, Polish-American Enterprise, 1990 (Box 33)
- Vice President for University Relations Correspondence, 1989-1996
  Vice President for University Relations Correspondence, 1989-1996 (1.0 linear feet), is comprised of outgoing correspondence (with some incoming letters attached) of Walter Harrison. The correspondence represents Harrison's duties first as executive director of University Relations and later as Vice President for University Relations with oversight for government relations. Correspondence consists mainly of letters written as a spokesman for the university and include letters to the editors of various area newspapers and responses written on behalf of the President. One folder of material, dated 1989-1990, details planning for a celebration in honor of former football coach and athletic director Bo Schembechler. The file includes a letter from Millie Schembechler.
  - "Bo Show" (Bo Schembechler Celebration), 1989-1990 (Box 38)
  - Outgoing Correspondence, 1989-1996; 11 folders (Box 38)